{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/1094","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1094","name":"Royal Skateland","address":"5201 Alter Rd.","zipcode":"48224","owner":"Mich. Skatelands, Inc.","licenseNumber":"035166","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-82.95610,42.39862","geojson":{"id":"1094","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-82.95610046,42.39862442]},"properties":{"name":"Royal Skateland","owner":"Mich. Skatelands, Inc.","address":"5201 Alter Rd.","zipcode":"48224","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"035166","establishmentid":"1094","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2022-04-01"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3465","name":"Club La Posse","address":"14911 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"5250","name":"Warren Fresh Fish","address":"14900 Warren E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"684","name":"Universal Coney Island","address":"14505 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48215"},{"establishmentid":"1467","name":"Saranda Coney Island","address":"15221 Warren Ave. E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"51623858","name":"Impresso Expresso","address":"5965 Mayburn","zipcode":"48127"},{"establishmentid":"839","name":"Hamilton Academy","address":"14223 Southampton Ave.","zipcode":"48213"},{"establishmentid":"1448","name":"Club Armane","address":"15000 Harper","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"1744","name":"Moe's Subway 2","address":"10601 Outer Dr. E.","zipcode":"48224"},{"establishmentid":"2395","name":"W. D. Alabama Style Food Service","address":"14929 Harper","zipcode":"48203"},{"establishmentid":"4711","name":"Lady Glorias","address":"14929 Harper","zipcode":"48224"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"61915","inspectionDate":"2023-03-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"at the bottom surfaces of Frozen coke machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"57288","inspectionDate":"2022-02-15T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FOOD PREP LINE","subLocation":"Floor panel of Equipment","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"Through out the day as necessary","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"54220","inspectionDate":"2021-02-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"50742","inspectionDate":"2020-02-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Counter(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-02-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Urinal(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"45001","inspectionDate":"2019-01-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s) at counter","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Cracked","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Cabinet(s) (lower)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Urinal(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"41460","inspectionDate":"2018-02-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Refrigerator/freezers","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"Inside the Ice machine","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37960","inspectionDate":"2017-02-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored with food-contact portion exposed","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"At the Single service items","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2017-02-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store inverted."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1094"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}